如果布鲁斯·班纳在开租来的车时
If Bruce Banner's driving a rental car
变身成了绿巨人浩克  车坏了保险赔吗
and turns into the Hulk, do you think he's covered,
还是租车时他得先加上浩克为附加驾驶才行
or does he need to add the Hulk as an additional driver?
你真的该交个女朋友了
You really need a girlfriend.
邮差先生来啦
Mailman's here!
还记得他当年看到我们也这个兴奋劲儿吗
Aw. Remember when he used to get at excited to see us?
有给谢尔顿·库珀博士的信吗
Do you have any mail for Dr. Sheldon Cooper?
有  不过我不能直接给你
I do, but I can't hand it right to you--
我必需得先放进邮箱里
I have to put it in the box.
这一点就能看出正经的美国邮政服务
And that is what separates the U.S. Postal Service
与快递公司不正经的快递员的差别
from those hippies at FedEx.
太好啦
Oh, goody!
什么东西让你这么兴奋
What is so exciting?
是沃尔科特博士寄来的信
It's a letter from Dr. Wolcott.
我们一直有通信讨论我的弦理论研究
We've been corresponding about my string theory research.
罗伯特·沃尔科特  沃尔科特定理的那个人吗
Wait. Robert Wolcott? Like Wolcott's Theorem Wolcott?
就是他
The very same.
他不是发疯然后跟所有人断绝联络了吗
Didn't he go crazy and cut off all contact with people?
对啊  他是因为被他的朋友
Yeah, he was driven mad by a friend
整天想聊浩克的汽车保险给逼疯的
who kept wanting to talk about the Hulk's car insurance!
他邀请我这周末去他的木屋
Oh. He's invited me to his cabin for the weekend,
聊聊他最近的新突破
to discuss a breakthrough he's had.
-他的什么木屋  -他隐居世外
- His cabin? - Yes. He lives off the grid,
住在山里
up in the mountains.
所以你要到渺无人烟的地方
So you're gonna go to the middle of nowhere
跟一个你素未谋面的疯子度过周末吗
and spend the weekend with a crazy man you've never met?
对啊  怎么了
Yes. Why?
没什么  玩得开心
No reason. Have fun.
第十一季  第二十集
厉害
Oh, nice one.
佩妮  你读书的时候听起来也是这样
Hey, Penny, that's what you sound like when you read.
-喂  -干嘛啦
- Hey! ?- What?
是他说的
He said it.
谢尔顿  你在干嘛
Sheldon, what are you doing?
我在解码沃尔科特博士的信
I am decoding Dr. Wolcott's letter
这本书是解密的密钥
using this book as the key.
用密语做的交谈是不是比普通的更有趣呢
Aren't conversations more fun when they're in code?
对的  但我的"对的"是"不对"的密语
Yes. But I'm using a code where "Yes" means "No."
我解出来了
Oh. I got it!
他给了我去他木屋的路线
He's given me directions to his cabin.
他有点太神经兮兮了吧
He seems a little paranoid.
他才没有神经兮兮
He is not paranoid.
-你在干嘛  -遵从他的指示
- What are you doing? - ?Following his instructions.
莱纳德  不许你让谢尔顿这周末独自赴会
Leonard, you are not letting Sheldon go alone this weekend.
我是大人了  我不需要谁来当我监护人
I am a grown man-- I don't need somebody to chaperone me.
我只需要他送我去  结束后接我回来
I just need him to drop me off, pick me up,
再帮我包一份午餐就行
and pack me a sack lunch.
别看我
Don't look at me.
当结束奏乐之时  牵着他的手的人是你
When the music stopped, you were holding Sheldon.
艾米不能带他去  她的单身女郎派对是这周末
Amy can't take him-- it's her bachelorette party this weekend.
是的呢
Yes, it is--
因为老娘要结婚啦
because I'm getting married!
你这一整个周末都打算这样吗
Are you gonna be doing that all weekend?
对  你知道为什么吗
Yes. Do you know why?
因为你要结婚啦
Because you're getting married!
好吧  莱纳德
All right, Leonard,
看来得你开车送我了
looks like you're driving me.
但你到时候在山脚下放我下就行了
But maybe you could drop me at the bottom of the mountain.
不想被他看见我要人送  都不酷了
I want him to think I'm cool.
太好了  大家周末都有安排
That's great, everyone's got weekend plans.
艾米有单身女郎派对
Amy has her bachelorette party,
谢尔顿要到森林里被人当狩猎的猎物
and Sheldon's gonna go to the woods and get hunted for sport.
身为每次他在宜家走丢时
Yeah, as someone who has to track him every time
负责找到他的专人
he gets lost in IKEA,
我感觉我也会是狩猎他的一把好手
I feel like I'd be really good at that.
莱纳德  你不能放他下车就走
Leonard, you cannot drop him off.
你得跟他待在一起确保他的安全
You have to stay with him and keep him safe.
-霍华德  你得去确保莱纳德的安全  -好吧
- Howard, you have to go and keep Leonard safe. ?- Fine.
我懂  你也想要我去确保霍华德的安全
I get it-- and you want me to go and keep Howard safe.
-其实我...  -你就说是  不然这家伙
- Actually, I... - ?Uh, just say yes, or he's gonna want
会要来我们的单身女郎派对
to come to the bachelorette party.
你确定这周末你可以吗
Are you sure you're gonna be okay this weekend?
当然啦
Of course.
其实我更担心的是你
No, I'm much more concerned about you.
我知道男人不在时  你们女人都是什么德行
I know how you gals behave when the men are away.
你知道吗
You do?
我读过诗人欧里庇得斯的《酒神的女信徒》
I've read The Bacchae by Euripides.
喝喝小酒  骑骑豹子
Drinking wine, riding panthers...
证明了女人野有着超过2500年的历史
Proof that girls have gone wild for over 2,500 years.
我也想跟你说不会发生那些事
Well, I wish I could say none of that is gonna happen,
但是是佩妮在筹办  而她也是我
but Penny is planning it, and she is the reason
会拥有屁股上有字的内裤的始作俑者
I own those underwear with writing across the butt.
凡事小心
Well, just be careful,
记得使用防护措施
and use protection.
你是觉得我们会做什么啊
What do you think is gonna happen?
我不知道啊  但周末艳阳高照
I don't know. But it's going to be sunny,
你又容易晒伤
and you burn easily.
我会没事的
It'll be fine.
我估计会喝点酒  跳点舞
I'm sure there'll be some drinking and some dancing,
然后会有个邮差出现
and then a mailman'll probably show up
开始脱掉他的衣服...
and take his clothes off...
尼古拉斯要来脱衣服吗
Nicholas is going to take his clothes off?
不是  不是我们的邮差
No, not our mailman.
是扮成邮差的舞者
A dancer pretending to be a mailman.
冒充联邦雇员吗
Impersonating a federal employee?
你们的庆功宴在哪举办  监狱吗
Oh, where's the after-party, prison?
你担心我的样子好有爱
It's sweet that you're worried about me.
我当然担心你啦
Well, of course I'm worried about you--
我希望你平平安安
I want you to be safe.
我也希望你平平安安
And I want you to be safe.
我会的  我的朋友们会陪着我
I will be. I'll have my friends with me.
如果出了什么事  我可以拿他们当人肉盾牌
If anything should go wrong, I can use them as human shields.
在人类历史中的大多数时候
For most of human history,
时间都被认为是现实客观存在的一部分
time was believed to be an objective part of reality.
但根据伊曼努尔康德的理论
But with the contributions of Immanuel Kant,
科学与哲学...
science and philosophy...
当我叫你搞个旅途歌单
When I said you should make a playlist for the road trip,
我是说让你找点音乐
I meant music.
这比音乐更好
This is better than music--
这是关于非线性时间的讲座呢
this is a lecture on nonlinear time.
听起来只是正常的时间而已
Sounds like it's just on regular time.
没错  但我调成了随机播放
Yes. But I put it on shuffle.
真好呀
This is nice.
我们四个人上次这样一起出行
The four of us haven't taken a trip like this
第9季第3集
还是莱纳德的单身派对
since Leonard's bachelor party.
现在到了谢尔顿的单身派对
And now here we are for Sheldon's.
没错  那个  莱纳德
Yeah, uh, Leonard...
作为谢尔顿的伴郎  我要通知你们
As Sheldon's best man, I need to inform you
这不是一个单身派对
that this is not a bachelor party.
告诉他们原因
And tell them why.
所以你这人碎碎念抱怨不停
Because you're a tiresome scold.
才怪  因为单身派对
No. It's because a bachelor party
是一场只追求肉体欢愉的
is typically a hedonistic blowout
享乐派对
where no pleasures of the flesh are denied.
我对此毫无兴趣
I'm not interested in that.
这和我刚才说的有什么区别
How is that not exactly what I said?
好了
Okay, now,
我向谢尔顿保证过今晚不会太疯狂
I promised Sheldon things weren't gonna get too crazy tonight.
我应该担心吗
Should I be worried?
你只需担心你要嫁的那个人
Oh, just about who you're marrying.
快来吧
Just come on.
欢迎来到你的...
Welcome to your...
单身派对
bachelorette party!
大家缝聚会
It's a quilting bee!
我的单身派对是大家缝聚会
My bachelorette party's a quilting bee!
是不是很完美
Isn't it perfect?
没错  抛开那些涂油脱衣舞男和性玩具
Yeah, instead of oiled-up strippers and sex toys,
我们认真地思考  艾米到底喜欢什么
we thought: what does Amy like?
艾米最爱大家缝聚会了
Amy likes the quilting bee!
这地方太诡异了
Well, this place is creepy.
为什么
Why?
你没看到他的菜园吗
Well, did you see his vegetable garden?
在四月种纯种番茄
Heirloom tomatoes in April.
太诡异了
Creepy.
好了听着
Okay, listen.
沃尔科特博士是顶尖的拓扑学家
Dr. Wolcott is a brilliant topologist.
我们得制定一些基本规则  免得你们丢脸
We need to set some ground rules so that you don't embarrass me.
不许变魔术  不许发牢骚
No magic. No whining.
还有你  什么都不许
You-- just no.
他怎么就能抱怨呢
Uh, how come he gets to whine?
沃尔科特博士
Dr. Wolcott?
沃尔科特博士  沃尔科特博士
Dr. Wolcott? Dr. Wolcott?
开了好多道锁呀
That's a lot of locks.
他也敲了好多次门  这俩是绝配
Mm. That was a lot of knocks-- they were made for each other.
-沃尔科特博士  -库柏博士
- Dr. Wolcott. ?- Dr. Cooper.
这些人是谁呀
Uh, who are these people?
他们是我的朋友  我在信里介绍过
Oh, these are my friends. I wrote about them in my letter.
信  我没收到过信呀
Oh, letter? I didn't get a letter.
我今早才把信寄出来
Well, that's because I just sent it this morning, you know?
看来是线性时间赢了
So score one for linear time. ?
我一般不允许陌生人进我的房子
Well, um, I don't normally allow strangers into my house.
但如果进来了  你也会放他们离开吧
But when you do, you-you let them out, right?
库珀博士  如果你能保证
Dr. Cooper, if you can promise me
这些人像你一样聪明又严谨
these men share your intellect and academic rigor,
那我可以让他们加入
yeah, I suppose they can join us.
你们可能得在车上等我了
You guys might need to wait in the car.
我来给你们介绍一下
Well, let me show you around.
这是我思考大部分事情时坐的椅子
This is the chair where I do most of my thinking,
用来思考工作上的事
my thinking about work.
思考那些待我不好的人时
Now, my thinking about people who have wronged me,
我坐那把椅子
I do over there.
我一直说我需要一把用来怨恨的椅子
I've always said that I should get a grudge chair.
-莱纳德   我是不是一直说呀  -你说了
- Leonard, have I not always said that? - Mm, you have--
-但你担心自己花太多时间在上面了  -对
- but you were worried you'd spend too much time in it. - Yeah.
这是真的
That was a real concern.
我的天  这个番茄太好吃了
Oh, my God, this tomato is amazing!
我可以像啃苹果一样吃掉它
I can eat it like an apple.
我的秘密就是用自己的粪便施肥
My secret is I fertilize it with my own manure.
这表情千金不换
The look on your face.
这微笑的弧度  想知道跟哪个部位的像吗
It's a sort of grin. You want to know what kind?
沃尔科特博士
So, Dr. Wolcott,
你信中提到  你有一种最新的数学理论
in your letter, you said you had a new mathematical approach
可以帮助我将弦理论中的维度概念化
that would help me conceptualize the dimensions in string theory?
没错没错  但我们开始前
Uh, yes, yes, yes, yes. But before we get started,
我需要先把每个人的手机没收了
I am going to need to collect everybody's phone.
为什么
Oh. ?Why?
因为他们可都是小型窃听器呢
Because they're little listening devices, aren't they?
可以被想盗取你成果的人利用
Yes, for people to spy on you and steal your work.
回想一下过去的好日子
Yeah, what happened to the good old days
如果想盗取你的心血
where if someone wanted to steal your work,
还得请个妓女来勾引你
they had to hire a prostitute to seduce you?
谁告诉你这件事的
Who told you about that?
我只是开个玩笑
Just making a joke.
真的发生的时候就没那么好笑了
Yeah, it's not funny when it happens.
好了
All right, now,
你可以先从这个笔记本开始
you're probably going to want to start with this notebook here.
-我的天  -开始吧
- Oh. Oh, my. ?- Here we are.
无意冒犯  沃尔科特博士  这内容无意义啊
no offense, Dr. Wolcott, but I'm not sure this makes any sense.
因为我都是倒着写的
That's because I've written it all backwards.
你  哦哇
You... Wow.
我这是倒着说的"哇哦"
That's "Wow" backwards.
那个...
Hmm. You know...
-我还是看不懂  -里面的数字其实是字母
- I still don't get it. - Well, plus the numbers are letters
字母其实是数字
and the letters are numbers. ?Oh.
我爱死他了
I love him.
你是不是玩得很开心
Are you having fun?
开心
Yeah.
刚缝好了上边到下边的部分
I just, uh, finished sewing this top to bottom.
现在要开始缝左右的
Now I'm gonna sew it side to side.
慢慢来
Pace yourself.
喝茶不
Some more tea?
太好了
Oh, lovely.
什么鬼啊  这都是啥玩意呀
Seriously? What the hell?
-怎么了  -怎么回事
- Huh? - ?What?
这是我的单身派对  喝茶和缝被子吗
This is my bachelorette party, tea and quilts?
你自己说不要太疯狂的
?Well, you said you didn't want anything crazy.
可我说的方式是  "我不要太疯狂的"
?Yes, but I said it like, "I don't want anything crazy."
意思就是我要疯  我要狂
Which clearly means I wanted something crazy.
难道你们眼中的我就是这么无趣吗
I mean, is this how boring you think I am?
佩妮  她在问你问题呢
Penny, she asked you a question.
当然不是了
Of course not.
所以你们觉得我喜欢缝被子吗
So you thought that I would like quilting?
-那你不喜欢吗  -当然喜欢了
- Well, don't you? - Of course I like quilting!
这是制作一床被子的最慢方式
It's the slowest way to make a blanket!
但这是我的单身女郎派对
But this is my bachelorette party!
那就应该放纵不羁  做些错误决定
It's supposed to be fun and wild and full of bad decisions.
我们当然可会做错误决定了
Hey, we can make bad decisions.
她接连生了两个孩子  我误以为你喜欢缝被子
She had two kids back-to-back and I thought you'd like this,
这还不算做错误决定吗
so we're off to a good start.
来吧  让我们找个地方
Come on, let's go somewhere we can do body shots
-在裸身酒保身上喝男体酒  -没错
- off shirtless bartenders. - ?Yes.
真的吗  会不会太过了
I don't know. That might be too much.
没错  那这样吧
All right, you know what,
我们还是留在家里喝点小酒...
why don't we stay home, have a little wine...
你们怎么就体会不到我的潜台词
What are you not getting about this?!
沃尔科特博士  您对时间的研究成果是革命性的
Dr. Wolcott, your work on time is revolutionary.
我想说谢谢你
I would say thank you,
但在我的时间理论中
but, in my theory of time,
你已经赞扬过我的成果具有革命性
you've already called my work revolutionary,
而我也已经谢过你了
I've already thanked you,
我不喜欢重复说一句话
and I hate repeating myself,
所以我就不说了
so let's move on.
等等  你是说时间和空间一样
Wait a minute, are-are you saying that time
都具有多维性吗
has multiple dimensions, the same as space?
不  不是我说的
No. No, I'm not saying it--
是数学计算说的
the math is saying it.
当然这个数学计算是我想出来的
Though it is the math that I invented,
所以我想也可以等同于我说的
so, yes, I guess I am saying it.
你能懂任何一点吗
You understanding any of this?
我从粑粑番茄之后就什么都搞不懂了
I haven't understood anything since poop tomato.
我的天
My goodness,
这真是太神奇了
this is incredible.
我就是想不出如何把弦理论代入其中
?See, I-I'm just not seeing where string theory fits into all this,
所以我想在这点上
and that's where I think that you and I
你和我可以一起合作
could be of help to each other.
谢谢  我真是荣幸
Thank you. I'd be honored.
我给你看看我最新的论文吧
All right. Allow me to show you my most recent journal.
谢尔顿说得对
Sheldon's right.
这家伙  真是个天才
This guy, this guy's brilliant.
没错  虽然他有点神经兮兮
Yeah, I mean, he's a little... kooky,
但他聪明到可以重新概念化时间
but a mind that can reconceptualize time
那么他用罐子收集自己剪下来的脚趾甲
probably has a reason for keeping a jar
一定也有我们无法理解的原因了
of toenail clippings that we just don't understand.
我光看他算的内容就能在这待上几个月
I could spend months up here just going through his math.
我想谢尔顿可能会
I think Sheldon might.
太棒了  谁去告诉艾米
Great. Who's gonna tell Amy
她的未婚夫被深山里的疯子抢走了
we lost her fiance to a madman in the mountains?
我出力开车了
Hey, I drove.
好令人激动呀
This is so exciting.
我们能不能喝男体酒
Can we do a body shot?
我一直想试试男体酒
I've always wanted to do a body shot.
还有  男体酒到底是什么
Also, what's a body shot?
就是你用陌生人的肚脐盛酒来喝
It's when you take a drink out of a stranger's belly button.
免了  谢谢
No, thanks.
如果他们肚脐外凸怎么办
What if they have an outie?
就流得到处都是吗
Does it just spill everywhere?
我们有一整晚时间
Okay, look, we've got all night.
放松点  我们可以...
Let's just take it easy. We can...
我要结婚啦
I'm getting married!
给  第一轮免费
Here you go. First round is on the house.
你好呀
Hey there.
你提供男体酒服务吗
Do you do body shots?
她说她不想玩这个了
Oh, she said she didn't want one.
少管闲事
Mind your business.
干杯
Cheers!
12分钟后
艾米
Amy?
艾米  我们要不要送她回家
Amy? Should we get her home?
为什么  她睡死了  我们又点了迷你汉堡
Why? She's sound asleep, and we have sliders coming.
再来一轮
One more round!
这在奇点的情况下
So, how would this work
会如何进行
in the context of a singularity?
这部分不好解释
Yes, that's-that's a tricky bit to explain.
你应该熟悉非阿尔贝群理论吧
I assume you're familiar with non-abelian group theory.
当然
Oh, and how.
你永远不会忘记第一次群理论
You never forget your first group theory.
各位  我去煮一壶咖啡
Listen, I'm gonna put on a pot of coffee,
有很多数学的部分得过一遍
because there is a lot of math to go through.
他还说他不想要狂野的单身派对
And he said he didn't want a wild bachelor party.
你说什么
Excuse me?
谢尔顿一个月后要结婚了
Oh, uh, Sheldon's getting married in a month.
恭喜你
Congratulations.
我也是已婚男人
Yeah, I'm a married man myself.
真的吗  妻子也在这儿吗
Oh, really? Is she here?
还活着吗
And alive?
除了你  其他人也能看到她吗
A-And can people other than you see her?
她住在慕尼黑
She lives in Munich.
这是完美的婚姻
It's a perfect marriage.
我们专注于自己的研究
We focus on our work
每年在生日的时候寄卡片给对方
and send each other cards every year on our birthdays.
等等  现在是几月
Hey, wait, what-what month is it?
四月
Uh, April.
几乎每年
Most years.
重点是  我们给彼此空间
The point is we give each other space.
我给她欧洲  她给我南美洲
I give her Europe, she gives me South America.
她以为我住在那儿
That's where she thinks I'm living.
我从没考虑过远距离婚姻
I-I've never considered a long-distance marriage.
听我说  如果你想成为伟大的科学家
Well, listen, if you want to be a great scientist,
就不能被分心
you can't afford to be distracted.
我怎么那么失礼
Hey, where are my manners?
你们一定饿了吧
You fellas must be hungry.
你们喜欢兔肉吗
Do you like rabbit?
-喜欢  -听起来不错
- ?Sure. ?- Sounds good.
那好
Okay.
但你们能分辨兔肉和松鼠肉的区别吗
But can you tell the difference between rabbit and squirrel?
-应该不行  -估计没办法
- ?Don't think so. - ?Probably not.
太棒了
Great!
我们今晚吃兔肉
We're having rabbit.
我去去就回
Be right back!
他通过脱离日常生活
It is amazing how much he's accomplished
获得了如此大的成就  实在太惊人了
by isolating himself from the distractions of day-to-day life.
拜托别告诉我你想过这样的生活
Okay, please don't tell me you want to live like this.
怪就怪在这儿
See, that's the strange thing.
我不想
I don't.
我有什么毛病啊
What is wrong with me?
我为什么不想要这种生活
Why don't I want this?
瞧这一切有多酷啊
Look at how cool it all is.
你没毛病  你有朋友
Nothing is wrong with you. You have friends,
有未婚妻  有完整的人生
you have a fiancee, you have a full life.
知道吗
You know what,
你说得对
you're right.
谢谢你们带我来这儿
Thank you for bringing me up here.
但我想我准备好回家了
But I think I'm ready to go home now.
真的吗  你不想留下来吃晚饭
Really? You don't want to stay for dinner
聊更多的科学吗
and talk more science?
不了  我们还是走吧
No. No, we better go.
我想念艾米了
I miss Amy.
还有我的手机
And my phone.
还有  我是德州人
Also, I'm from Texas,
我能尝得出兔肉和松鼠肉的区别
and I can taste the difference between rabbit and squirrel.
看谁重返人间啦
Oh, look who's back!
她醒了
There she is!
发生了什么  我们怎么到这儿的
What happened? How did we get here?
你什么都不记得了吗
You don't remember anything?
我记得喝了一些烈酒  然后
I remember taking some shots, and then...
就断片了
that's it.
天啊  我醉倒了吗
Oh, my gosh, did I pass out?
貌似是的
You kind of did.
在我自己的单身女郎派对上吗
At my own bachelorette party?
我真是逊爆了
I'm so lame.
你醉倒前还是做了
Well, you didn't pass out before you did
各种好玩的事呀
all kinds of fun stuff.
我做了什么
What did I do?
你做了什么啊
What did you do?
她做了什么
What'd she do?
爱尔兰传统踢踏舞舞剧
你不记得在吧台上跳《大河之舞》了吗
well, you don't remember Riverdancing on top of the bar?
我跳了吗
I did that?
当然了
Yeah, you did!
但我不会跳《大河之舞》啊
But I don't know how to Riverdance.
那也没能拦住你教那些半裸的消防员
Didn't stop you from teaching all those shirtless firemen.
我看见半裸消防员了吗
I saw shirtless firemen?
看见  闻过  还把他们当钢管滑下来
Saw, smelled, slid down like a pole.
我有没有露奶给某人看
Did I flash anybody?
应该问有没有给所有人看
How about everybody?
真不敢相信  我觉得好羞愧
I can't believe it. I'm so embarrassed.
你们没拍照吧
You didn't take any pictures, did you?
我们绝不会那样对你
Oh, no, we would never do that to you.
对啊  但如果有照片
Yeah. But if there were pictures,
一定狂野极了
they would be crazy.
你们真是我的好朋友
You guys are good friends.
晚饭来啦
Dinner!
人呢
Guys?
他们竟然不告而别
I can't believe they left without saying good-bye.
等一下  万一他们窃取了我的研究呢
Wait a minute, what if they stole my work?
等一下
Wait a minute!
万一他们根本没来过呢
What if they were never here at all?
等一下
Wait a minute!
万一他们还没来到
What if they haven't gotten here yet
但已经在路上了呢
but they're on their way?!
我还是赶紧收拾收拾
I better tidy up.
你好啊
Hello.
欢迎回家  怎么样了
Welcome back. How'd it go?
沃尔科特博士关于时间的理论
Well, Dr. Wolcott's theories of time
或许能拯救我对弦理论的新解读
might save my new interpretation of string theory.
真令人激动
Oh, well, that's exciting.
确实
It is.
你的单身女郎派对怎么样
How was your bachelorette party?
我到酒吧去了
Well, I was in a bar,
还看到一些半裸的男人
and I saw some shirtless men.
他们是消防员  为我展开了激烈的争夺
They were firemen, and they fought over me.
但在胜利者得到我送的战利品前
But Penny and Bernadette got me out of there
佩妮和伯纳黛特就把我带走了
before the victor got my spoils.
知道了
I see.
怎么了
What's the matter?
你好像闷闷不乐的
You look glum.
艾米  如果我不是你以为的那种人
Amy, would you still love me
你还会爱我吗
if I wasn't who you thought I was?
你在说什么呢
What are you talking about?
如果我其实不是
Well, what if it turns out
你当初爱上的那个专心致志  沉迷科学
I'm not the single-minded, science-obsessed recluse
把研究看得比一切人事物都重要的隐士
who puts his work above everything and everybody else
怎么办
that you fell in love with?
如果我不是你以为的那个
What if I'm not the straightlaced,
严厉刻板  沉默寡言的缝被女王  怎么办
buttoned-up, quilting queen you thought I was?
如果我是个
What if I'm a...
跳《大河之舞》的狂野女人呢
Riverdancing wild woman?
我依然会爱你
I'd still love you.
我也依然会爱你
I'd still love you, too.
你真的会跳《大河之舞》吗
Do you really know how to Riverdance?
你来告诉我啊
You tell me.
你不许跳给其他男人看
I'm the only man you do that for.